I don't know what I'm talking about
I just wanted to record somewhere that
wasn't she don't really know why I'm
recording excuse like random thoughts
which is what I usually do on my private
part of Facebook to record to have it
there but not have to store it somewhere
and this is where I'm or actually I
don't do much here I don't know how to
utilize my YouTube channel to its full
extent or any extent really because it
doesn't work or like I don't seem to be
able to do like a video every week and
post it in the same way it feels okay to
do live ones because I'm not expected to
edit them then people don't watch them
anyway whatever cares something will
find it for supposed to find it but that
how much I'm getting the message that
I'm supposed to I don't and that like
why I don't want to share it and why
it's like I don't want to look crazy and
I don't want to have people judge me and
I have to not care about that so I don't
have to be do anything I'm just not
going to care about pay for there's
something higher than me that I'm
following and I don't even know what it
is I don't know whether it's God I don't
know if it's internal I don't know if
it's sight like there's something and it
leaves clues and you follow them and
life is amazing no matter all of the
struggles that I'm going through and
have went through are exactly who when
where I'm supposed to be for me I don't
know if that's the same message everyone
gets when they sit still and listen to
themselves I don't know if everyone else
has a deep calling and I think no but
everyone does that's the point
that's like then I get to be one of the
people to awaken it in other people or
kickstart the thing that awakes it in
other people that's amazing
I am enjoying it I'm enjoying the
process but then in trying to explain
OTT just the concept I think that's
doing its own thing on the website where
I'm explaining it to the best of my
ability to explain it but this other
piece that I'm like it's not as
important we don't really need to share
that is as important and I do need to
share it that like that we need to get
along that we need it and I can only
kind of share my experience cuz I'm not
an expert and getting along with people
but then I truly don't sometimes I don't
my mind goes blank I'm just like four
thoughts it's hard to pick which one the
world is so divided and we're reacting
to stuff in a way that isn't serving us
isn't serving anybody else it's not
serving each other and it's on all
fronts all of the time
and so we get mad about people getting
mad because we're mad we act out of fear
or we don't want to act out of fear
because that's weakness so we projected
and have a moat remote
everything like we're humans having a
human experience and instead of owning
that we have to like put the shell
around ourselves and be who or not and
there's so much wasted there because I
don't making sense don't pick something
else talk low but to just yes that seems
like a random and I mean okay you know
Kay that it's random but I'm day message
I'm supposed to share more of my story
and myself not because it's important to
the project necessarily more because
there's things in myself that I hide
because I want to be more appealing to a
greater audience because this thing
needs a greater audience and I want this
thing to exist and the more in the real
world in the my everyday life I realized
who I am and become more myself the
happier I am and the more I'm able to
easily contribute to people and
communities in a way that I wasn't able
to before and I had to like I had to
accept myself there was no other choice
I basically medically had to and so I
don't know like I want to give that to
people but I also get the world and I
wasn't there wasn't talking about that
was I talk about something else
so what's legal now and the one of the
stopping points of me doing this and
coming on camera more often is that I
don't really want to appear on camera
stoned but I'm going to be because I was
I mean it was legal for me anyway I had
a prescription but I wasn't comfortable
doing it that way like seeing other
people doing videos with a beer in their
hand or something that's no problem
that's totally normal and part of our
society but having I don't know but the
stigma and everything like I smoked pot
a lot I smoked it daily every day I
smell good and it is my relationship
with it is mine like it's that's part of
my journey that's part of its it's
medicine and it helps me in a lot of
ways it also is an addiction and yet
it's my medicine and I have permission
advice too like I'm supposed to smoke it
during the day and you know like it
helps my body to not be in pain but it
also helps my life to not function quite
so well and there's times where I want
to smoke it during the day and pretty
much I never do well I never don't want
to smoke it during the day like it's I
have cravings and so it's an addiction
that I'm I'm balancing but yeah it's
helped I mean it's not like it's
anything it's helped and hindered this
process the whole way but it's just a
thing it's just it's a tool and I'm
gonna use it for good and I'm gonna have
compassion with myself and I am having
that's the piece of my journey I want to
share because I want other people to
have access to it but I don't know how
to give people access to it that you get
to be imperfect and exist in the world
and not just exist but thrive and be
happy
you're not unworthy of love and
connection and a family because you have
an addiction because you change or are
low in one mental capacity or emotional
capacity we are a diverse human species
and we have to honor that
there's a piece that's my journey my
journey alone I can hear my kids TV show
it's what they gotta bother me pickles
can you turn that down please
because and I can't turn myself up
that's not gonna work oh no that's
locked for a reason
okay leave it out there please I'm on
camera and you're not so that's not
happening awesome
I am on video live right now please put
it by the door and that like I'm scared
to be on when she's here because I don't
want any track with her and I don't I go
put it by the door
that sounds bad
she's presents probably like 50 times a
day I just says I'm wonderful and I love
it and I need to find an earplug okay
I'll just get up and get into your plug
and go and do that right now I know I
guess I could have also took there to
turn it down
would have been awful like to not be
seen perfect
parenting imperfectly and yet yeah it's
a piece of myself is really gross
not a good one why okay I'm getting off
I can't see it with the sound and such
but that's that's a piece of what I want
to share without how I was doing it
previously which was I don't know it was
about was and it was different
to be losing your train of thought every
five seconds yeah great okay
I can't listen to both of those things
at the same time but sharing my like
medical journey sharing me by my
interpersonal journey and my insights on
the world I'll probably start sharing
more of that all right bye-bye
am i parenting that